





# **Danny Huang**

+61 452504531 | dannyhuang1234@gmail.com | NZ Citizen

## **Professional summary**

**Full-stack Developer** currently working as a **Cloud Engineer at National Australia Bank** with a background in **Electrical Engineering specialising in Machine Learning.** Built and deployed **multiple ReactJS web application** from **scratch to production** for NAB bankers utilising AWS services. Heavily involved as a Quantitative Trader hobbiest developing **Recurrent Neural Network models** for predictive analysis.

#### Education

# The University of Melbourne

Melbourne, VIC, Australia

M.Eng, Major: Electrical Engineering, specialising in Optimisation and Machine Learning

Jan 2019- December 2020

- WAM:81.6%, First Class Honours
- Thesis: Optimal path-planning/following for Autonomous Vehicles using Partial Environment Information
- Award: 2<sup>nd</sup>-place People's Choice Award. ( /182 Final Year teams)
  - 3<sup>rd</sup>-place Road to Endeavour Award. ( /182 Final Year teams)

B.S, Major: Electrical Engineering

February 2016-December 2018

WAM:76.1%, Second Class Honours Division A

**Exchange Program** 

Los Angeles, USA

University of California, Los Angeles

September 2017-June 2018

Technical GPA:3.12

## **Work Experience**

## **National Australia Bank**

• Associate Cloud (Software) Engineer – Business Lending

01/06/2021 - Present Full-Time

• Junior Cloud (Software) Engineer – Business Lending

11/01/2021-01/06/2021 Full-Time

- Full-stack web application development using Backend For Frontend(BFF) alongside DevOps role and Unit Testing using ReactJS, Typescript, GraphQL,PostgresQL, Jest, Enzyme.
- o Built 3 production ready web applications used by all bank branches in Australia.
- Setup CI/CD Jenkins pipeline infrastructure for app deployment integrating quality checks such as SonarQube, Checkmarx and Deputy.
- Mentored external contractors (Accenture & DXC) NAB-specific UI development.
- Completed internal 2 week hackathon building app on house price evaluation using Machine Learning (Convolutional Neural Network) based on current housing market features (No.Rooms, carspace, proximity to facilities etc.).
- Full stack developer confident in ReactJS, AWS infrastructure hosting, serverless and scalable solutions (e.g. ECS, DynamoDB, autoscaling etc).

## **Jacobs Engineering Consultancy**

26/11/2019- 21/02/2020 Full-Time

• Undergraduate Electrical Engineer (Rolling Stock)

22/02/2020-01/11/2020 Part-Time

- Assisted in a 200k life extension project for V/Line in data analysis for fault finding and providing recommendations to the client.
- Worked on a \$600 billion dollar project for Victorian Government 2050 metro vision procuring rolling stock(trains) in a consortium of 4 engineering consultancies and government agency.
- o Time-managed 4 concurrent projects ensuring deadlines are met.
- o Prepared 5 final reports for clients in a span of 3 months.
- o Independent on site-visit to client to inspect project progression and updates.

#### Commonwealth Scientific and Industrial Research Organisation (CSIRO)

19/11/2018-01/03/2019

#### Vacation Student Researcher - InterFloat

- Develop & test capacitive sensing method to measure properties of mineral solution within the flotation
- Use SPICE simulation to develop circuits, Schematic design & PCB layout for test.
- Laboratory based circuit assembly & practical test.







# **Danny Huang**

+61 452504531 | dannyhuang1234@gmail.com | NZ Citizen

### **Project Design**

#### Building a ReactJS App hosting on AWS - Workshop

2021 working at NAB

Designed and taught a ReactJS workshop to University students teaching them how to create web app and host on AWS using AWS services specifically S3, DynamoDB, Elastic Load Balancer, Elastic Container Service.

#### Optimal path-planning for autonomous vehicles using partial information

Capstone 2020

- Develop novel advanced control strategies (via machine learning) for autonomous driving (minimise lap time, power consumption, and guarantee collisions avoidance) with partial information of the environment.
- Real-time collision avoidance for static and dynamic obstacles using Mixed-Integer Quadratic Programming.
- Object Identification
- Designed novel optimisation-based controller using SLAM (Simultaneous Localisation and Mapping) that ensures real-time optimal car maneuvering, speed, and safety.

# **Algorithmic Trading U.S Market Equity Strategy**

Year-long Personal Project 2020-2021

Research/develop/test trading strategies using signal indictor and Neural Network models. Backtesting strategies on BackTrader platform in Python with a sharpe ratio of 1.2.

#### Al Planning for Autonomy

Semester 1 2020

 Developed full autonomous agent with 3 other students for Pac-man game that ensures completion based on time/score/ghost avoidance.

### Measuring froth depth in flotation units

Summer Internship 2019

Research Assistant-develop & test capacitive sensing. Schematic design & PCB layout for test. Written Report describing work and outcomes. Verbal presentation describing results and experience.

**Exoskeleton** Semester 2 2018

 Student-based proof of Concept designing light-weight and Inexpensive exoskeleton that assists human body movement and **research** into human mechanisms in order to provide assistance efficiently.

#### **Controller for Self-driving Car**

Spring Quarter 2018

• Designed a controller that allows a model car to adjust its position relative to its projected position in order to stay in track (lane keeping).

# **Speech Classification**

 Designed a deep neural network algorithm that detects, trains, and predicts audio signal speech recognition of male/female voices with 99.4% accuracy.

#### **Technical Skills**

## **Frontend Tech Stack**

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Typescript, ReactJS, React Native, Jest, Enzyme

#### **Backend Tech Stack**

Python, Pandas, Java, C, SQL, MATLAB, TensorFlow, Sagemaker, Keras, DynamoDB, NoSQL, PostgreSQL, EC2, S3, GraphQL

# **DevOps Tech Stack**

Jenkins, Docker, ECS, Kong, Nginx

#### Hardware

FPGA, PCB Design, Soldering PCB & Dev board, Microchip SAM C MCU, Arduino Uno, Raspberry Pi

#### **Amazon Web Services (AWS) Certification**

- Machine Learning Specialty
- Solutions Architect Associate
- Cloud Practitioner

# Leadership & Extra-Curricular

# Coffee Appreciation for Enthusiasts – Social Media Director

09/2019-Present

Managing society's social media accounts with weekly posts on events and meetups whilst directing 2 supporting officers.









# **Danny Huang**

+61 452504531 | dannyhuang1234@gmail.com | NZ Citizen

# References

**Satbir Singh** 

Engineer Manager National Australia Bank 700 Bourke St, Melbourne

Work:+61 426219200

Email: satbir.singh@nab.com.au

**Luke Gibbons** 

Senior Rolling Stock Engineer Jacobs Engineering

452 Flinders St, Melbourne

Work:+61 402316692

Email:Luke.Gibbons@jacobs.com

Joseph Tey

Associate Engineer National Australia Bank 700 Bourke St, Melbourne

Work: +61 490026896

Email: joseph.tey@nab.com.au

**Tim Buchanan** 

Principle Rolling Stock Engineer

Jacobs Engineering

452 Flinders St, Melbourne

Work: +61 409225677

Email:tim.buchanan1@jacobs.com